[
	{
    	"id": "602",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these are not offered as RDS OLTP database types?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server",
        	"Oracle",
        	"My SQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"Aurora",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"DB2"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["DB2"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "603",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "What is AWS's RDS OLAP Data Warehouse offering?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server",
        	"Oracle",
        	"My SQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"Aurora",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Red Shift"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Red Shift"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "604",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a NoSQL database like DynamoDB, what is the equivalent to a table in an RDS?",
      	"answers": [
        	"collection",
        	"document",
        	"key/value pair",
        	"row",
        	"element"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["collection"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "605",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a NoSQL database like DynamoDB, what is the equivalent to a row in an RDS?",
      	"answers": [
        	"collection",
        	"document",
        	"key/value pair",
        	"table",
        	"element"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["document"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "606",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In a NoSQL database like DynamoDB, what is the equivalent to a field in an RDS?",
      	"answers": [
        	"collection",
        	"document",
        	"key/value pair",
        	"table",
        	"element"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["key/value pair"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "607",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which type of AWS database is primarily used for business intelligence?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server",
        	"Oracle",
        	"My SQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"Aurora",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Red Shift"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Red Shift"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "608",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which type of AWS database is used to pull in very large and complex data sets?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server",
        	"Oracle",
        	"My SQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"Aurora",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Red Shift"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Red Shift"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "609",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is not an OLAP type of database?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server Reporting Services",
        	"Cognos",
        	"Jaspersoft",
        	"Oracle Hyperion",
        	"SAP NetWeaver",
        	"MariaDB"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["MariaDB"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "610",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is an example of an OLTP query?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Query order number 1234, returns a row of data",
        	"Query net profit for EMEA and Pacific for digital radio product; returns large number of records"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Query order number 1234, returns a row of data"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "611",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is an example of an OLAP query?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Query order number 1234, returns a row of data",
        	"Query net profit for EMEA and Pacific for digital radio product; returns large number of records"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Query net profit for EMEA and Pacific for digital radio product; returns large number of records"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "612",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is not a type of Elasticache open-source in-memory caching engine?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Memcached",
        	"Redis",
        	"Hana"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Hana"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "613",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which port does MySQL listen on?",
      	"answers": [
        	"3306",
        	"3603",
        	"3300"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["3306"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "614",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "To have an EC2 instance access an RDS instance that is internal facing, the EC2 instance and the RDS instance must be in the same _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Security Group",
        	"ACL",
        	"WAF",
        	"AZ"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Security Group"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "615",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these is not a type of backup for RDS?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Automated backups",
        	"Database snapshots",
        	"Storage gateway"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Storage gateway"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "616",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS automated backups allow you to recover your database to any point in time within a ____________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Retention period",
        	"Backup window",
        	"Region",
        	"AZ"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Retention period"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "617",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS automated backups will take a full daily snapshot and will also store __________ throughout the day?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Transaction logs",
        	"Recovery volumes",
        	"Database logs",
        	"Access logs"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Transaction logs"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "618",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you do an RDS recovery, AWS will first choose the most recent daily backup, and then apply __________ relevant to that day?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Transaction logs",
        	"Recovery volumes",
        	"Database logs",
        	"Access logs"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Transaction logs"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "619",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you do an RDS recovery, you can do a point-in-time recovery down to the __________, within the ____________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"second, retention period",
        	"minute, retention period",
        	"second, business day",
        	"minute, business day"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["second, retention period"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "620",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS automated backups are not enabled by default?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "621",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS backups are taken within a __________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"Defined window",
        	"random window",
        	"specific timeframe",
        	"AWS defined timeframe"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Defined window"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "622",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "During the RDS backup window, storage IO may be ________ while your data is being backed up and you may experience ____________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"suspended, elevated latency",
        	"halted, elevated latency",
        	"disabled, an outage",
        	"accelerated, performance improvement"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["suspended, elevated latency"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "623",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS database snapshots are ________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"done manually, i.e. user initiated",
        	"done automatically",
        	"done randomly",
        	"not done at all"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["done manually, i.e. user initiated"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "624",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS database snapshots are ________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"stored even after you delete the original RDS instance, unlike automated backups",
        	"deleted along with the original RDS instance, as are automated backups",
        	"never deleted",
        	"stored forever"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["stored even after you delete the original RDS instance, unlike automated backups"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "625",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Whenever you restore either an automated backup or a manual snapshot, the restored version of the database will ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"be a new RDS instance",
        	"be the same RDS instance"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["be a new RDS instance"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "626",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Whenever you restore either an automated backup or a manual snapshot, the restored version of the database will be a new RDS instance with ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"a new DNS endpoint",
        	"the same DNS endpoint"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["a new DNS endpoint"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "627",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS encryption at rest is supported for all of these but which?",
      	"answers": [
        	"MySQL",
        	"Oracle",
        	"SQL Server",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Aurora",
        	"DB2"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["DB2"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "628",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS encryption is done using the __________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"AWS Key Management Service (KMS)",
        	"Customer Provided Key Management Service (CMS)"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["AWS Key Management Service (KMS)"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "629",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Once your RDS instance is encrypted, the data stored at rest in the underlying storage is encrypted, as are its automated backups, read replicas, and snapshots?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "630",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "You can encrypt an existing RDS database?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "631",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In order to use encryption for an existing RDS database, you must first create a ________, make a copy of that ________, and then _______ the copy?",
      	"answers": [
        	"snapshot, snapshot, encrypt",
        	"backup, backup, encrypt",
        	"snapshot, snapshot, restore"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["snapshot, snapshot, encrypt"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "632",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When working with RDS you never deal with ip addresses, you use the _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"RDS endpoint, which is a DNS endpoint",
        	"RDS database name",
        	"the VPC endpoint where the RDS is located",
        	"the DNS name of its EC2 instance"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["RDS endpoint, which is a DNS endpoint"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "633",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS multi-AZ allows you to have an exact copy of your production database in another AZ?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "634",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "AWS does not handle the replication for you in Multi-AZ mode?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "635",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS multi-AZ replication is done ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"synchronously",
        	"asynchronously"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["synchronously"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "636",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "In the event of planned database maintenance, DB instance failure, or an AZ failure, RDS will automatically to the standby so that database operations can resume quickly without admin intervention?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "637",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these RDS features is used for disaster recovery?",
      	"answers": [
        	"multi-AZ",
        	"read replicas"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["multi-AZ"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "638",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these RDS features is used for performance improvement?",
      	"answers": [
        	"multi-AZ",
        	"read replicas"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["read replicas"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "639",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these RDS databases does not use mutlti-AZ?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SQL Server",
        	"Oracle",
        	"MySQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Aurora"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["Aurora"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "640",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Aurora does not need mutlti-AZ because ________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"is spread across multiple AZ by default",
        	"it's serverless",
        	"it's a NoSQL database"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["is spread across multiple AZ by default"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "641",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Read replicas are populated by using _________ replication from the primary RDS database?",
      	"answers": [
        	"asynchronous",
        	"synchronous"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["asynchronous"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "642",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Read replicas are used for primarily _________ workloads?",
      	"answers": [
        	"read-heavy",
        	"write-heavy",
        	"high latency"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["read-heavy"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "643",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which of these does not support read replicas?",
      	"answers": [
        	"MySQL",
        	"PostgreSQL",
        	"MariaDB",
        	"Aurora",
        	"SQL Server"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["SQL Server"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "644",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "RDS read replicas are used for ________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"scaling",
        	"DR"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["scaling"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "645",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "To deploy a read replica you must have ________ turned on?",
      	"answers": [
        	"automatic backups",
        	"multi-AZ",
        	"snapshots"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["automatic backups"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "646",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "There is a limit of how many read replica copies (5) you can have of an RDS database?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["true"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "647",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "You can't have read replicas of read replicas?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "648",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you have read replicas of read replicas you have to watch out for ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"latency",
        	"contention"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["latency"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "649",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Each read replica will have its own ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"DNS endpoint",
        	"ip address"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["DNS endpoint"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "650",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "You can't have read replicas that have multi-AZ enabled?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "651",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "You can't create read replicas of multi-AZ source databases?",
      	"answers": [
        	"true",
        	"false"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["false"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "652",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you promote a read replica to be its own database you break its what?",
      	"answers": [
        	"replication",
        	"multi-AZ"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["replication"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "653",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Can you have a read replica in a second region?",
      	"answers": [
        	"yes",
        	"no"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["yes"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "654",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "DynamoDB supports both ______ and ________ data models?",
      	"answers": [
        	"document and key/value",
        	"document and relational",
        	"key/value. and relational"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["document and key/value"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "655",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "DynamoDB is stored on ______ storage?",
      	"answers": [
        	"SSD",
        	"HDD",
        	"Magnetic"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["SSD"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "656",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "DynamoDB is spread across ___________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"3 geographically distinct datacenters",
        	"3 AZs",
        	"3 regions"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["3 geographically distinct datacenters"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "657",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      	"question": "DynamoDB has which types of reads?",
      	"answers": [
        	"eventually consistent",
        	"strongly consistent",
        	"immediately consistent",
        	"instantaneously consistent"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["eventually consistent", "strongly consistent"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "658",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which type of DynamoDB read is the default?",
      	"answers": [
        	"eventually consistent",
        	"strongly consistent"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["eventually consistent"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "659",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which type of DynamoDB read is faster?",
      	"answers": [
        	"eventually consistent",
        	"strongly consistent"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["eventually consistent"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "660",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Which type of DynamoDB read returns a result that reflects all writes that received a successful response prior to the read?",
      	"answers": [
        	"eventually consistent",
        	"strongly consistent"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["strongly consistent"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "661",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "Why is DynamoDB considered better for read-heavy applications versus write-heavy applications?",
      	"answers": [
        	"it performs faster with reads",
        	"writes are eventually consistent",
        	"reads are far less expensive (price) than writes"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["reads are far less expensive (price) than writes"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "662",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "What other purchase option is available for DynamoDB?",
      	"answers": [
        	"reserved capacity",
        	"spot capacity"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["reserved capacity"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "663",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "With DynamoDB, what can you change on the fly through the console?",
      	"answers": [
        	"read write capacity",
        	"allocated memory",
        	"provisioned throughput"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["read write capacity"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "664",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "You can use push button scaling with which type of AWS database?",
      	"answers": [
        	"DynamoDB",
        	"RDS"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["DynamoDB"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "665",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you use push button scaling with DynamoDB you have _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"no downtime",
        	"marginal downtime",
        	"downtime"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["no downtime"]
    	}
  	},
  	{
    	"id": "666",
    	"category": "Cloud Concepts",
    	"info": {
      	"subcategory": "Databases",
      	"questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      	"question": "When you scale RDS you have _________?",
      	"answers": [
        	"no downtime",
        	"marginal downtime",
        	"downtime"
      	],
      	"correctAnswer": ["downtime"]
    	}
  	}
 ]
